freeadswebsites.com 2013-03-24

# Privacy Policy | Free Ads Websites | Free Ads | Free Ads Websites | Free Classified

This privacy policy helps you understand the handling of your personal information you share with us. We collect and use your personal information to aid our website and keep it safe (details are given below) in formal terms, our free ads website acting itself and through its subsidiaries are the data controllers of your personal information that you provide us with. Collection of your personal information

**1: Collection of your personal information:**

The personal information we collect from you is for various purposes and are not publicly visible (depends on your wish). We collect your personal information in order to avoid spam and fake ads being posted on our free ads website. Our servers are located around the globe and the personal information we collect from you is secure and will be not shared or sold to third parties but we can use your personal information in order to provide you with better services and improve our free ads website. The personal information we demand from our user is

Email address and IP address

Physical contact information like cell phone number and your residence

Computer sign on data, your browsing history and standard web log information

**2: Use of your personal information**

We use the personal information you provide us with for following purposes:

1: In order to provide you with our services to make your experience with us even better

2: Help the user in any dispute and problems you face

3: To encourage the user in safe trading and making our policies stronger

4:  To notify the user about any important recent activity or new services

5: Communicate with the market and bring promotional offers to user

6: To perform other tasks for the

Physical contact information like cell phone number and your residence

Computer sign on data, your browsing history and standard web log information

**3: Cookies:**

Our free ads website use cookies and other web beacon sin order you provide you with better services that will be aiding your business with us by helping your buying and selling on this platform.

What are cookies?

Cookies are defined as small files those exist in the hard drive of your computer. Our free ads classifieds website uses both types of cookies the persistent and session cookies in order to provide our users with series and assuring the safety of our users personal information. One thing to be mentioned here that session cookies are the types of cookies those are eliminated (not stored on your hard drive) when your browsing session have ended or your browser is closed

How we use cookies:

Our free ads website uses cookies for the following purposes:

Helping the user to enter your password fewer times during an unfinished browsing session

Providing you with information related to your interests

To upstate and insist on trust and safety

By the use of cookies we are able to offer many features and services for your benefit

To analyze our site`s traffic

**4: Disclosure:**

Please note the following for your convenience:

All the data that have is stored by our free ads website is treated strictly confidential and we never use, share, sell or rent the personal information that our users trust us with

We may user the personal information that the user provide us with to investigate any suspected ad that has been posted to make sure that it is not fake and spam

Our free ads website may use the personal information that our user provide us with in order to enforce our policies and act in response to claims that a posting is violating our policies

Note: We recommend you to visit our privacy policy page to time to be acknowledged with any changes been made to our privacy terms to avoid any kind of misunderstandings and problems in future. If you are a signed user than whenever this policy page is update you will be alerted and will be suggested to take a look at our new policies

Disclaimer: we like to mention here that the writing material and images being posted on our website is not the property of our free ads website and we are not responsible of it. The ad poster is truly responsible for such ads which are violating any truly and regulations and in such cases the dads and user account can be terminated.
